Today’s news is about Gao Kao.
Nowadays Chinese students have a lot of stress.
Piles of homework, never-ending weekend classes, competitive exams, and no doubt the gaokao leads to enormous pressure for Chinese students to succeed.
What do you suggest to relieve all of that stress?
I personally like drawing, and walking in nature.
But there are also other ways to relieve stress.
This year, Chinese students are again getting creative with their stress relief methods.
I already heard from the news how Chinese students are taking creative graduation photos.
How are students being creative with stress relief?
Well, my favorite way is balloon-stomping.
Students in Hefei, Anhui stomped balloons before taking the gaokao.
The excitement surely made them forget about the difficulty of the exam.
That’s a great way! Were they allowed to stomp the balloons at school?
Yes. As a matter of fact, most of these stress-relief methods require the school’s support.
For example, students sitting the gaokao at a school in Hengshui, Hebei all received ten yuan before taking each test.
That’s very generous!
There are also other ways, such as massages at school, and student-teacher activities on the sports field.
It all sounds like a lot of fun!